(Howard:)That's a kick.
(Howard:)That's an actual kick.
(Bernadette:)What are you doing?
(Howard:)I felt a kick.
(Howard:)There's a baby in there.
(Bernadette:)Oh, yeah, that's where I put it.
(Howard:)Oh, I mean, I know
you're pregnant.
(Howard:)I just...
(Howard:)never connected
the idea of pregnancy
(Howard:)and you actually having a baby.
(Bernadette:)Which MIT did you go to?
(Howard:)Oh, God, we are not ready
to have an infant in this house!
(Howard:)We don't have a crib,
we don't have diapers.
(Howard:)We're not baby-proofed.
(Howard:)Anyone can just walk in off the
street and lift our toilet lids!
(Bernadette:)Howie, we have time
to do all that stuff.
(Howard:)Do we?
(Howard:)Look at you.
(Howard:)Willy Wonka would roll you
to the juicing room.